

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER
AND TRAINEE

Details

Poland +48729668414 rohzxz@gmail.com

Skills

JavaScript Es6+

React

nextjs

HTML5

CSS3

Git

GitHub

tailwind css

redux tollkit

Links

portfolio

linkedin

<u>GitHub</u>

Hobbies

watching TV shows, movies

Languages

English

Profile

computer software student who's always eager to learn modern technologies. Familiar with Programming languages, database systems, electronics, and networking. Have self-research on some popular tools and frameworks used in IT markets. I have lived in Poland last two years. right now I am learning core Javascript and full stack development path. I am a good learner... I like to learn new things. and I m fascinated by this industry.

Employment History

Non-Commercial experience:

2020 - 2023

please check out my portfolio. recently I made it. and projects also

https://rohzxz.netlify.app/

java-script, React, HTML5, CCS3, Web development boot-camp

- · Constantly learning and improving. ...
- · Keeping up to date with the industry. ...

Technician Assist, stog.sp zoo, poland

DECEMBER 2021 - JULY 2022

Analysis of PCB motherboard, Add and Update Software. Creating, maintaining, and entering information into databases.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, degree , Maharshi Dayanand Sarswati University Ajmer,india

OCTOBER 2015 - JULY 2017

The full form of BCA is a bachelor's in Computer Application. BCA is a 3-year undergraduate degree program that focuses on knowledge of the basics of computer application and software development. The course of BCA includes database management systems, operating systems, software engineering, web technology and languages such as HTML, CSS, Java etc.

hospitality and management, SDH INSTITUTE, Singapore, Singapore

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2021

skills and knowledge in people management, service delivery, leadership, finance and marketing, as well as identifying, understanding and responding to the needs of clients.

Courses

HTML5, CCS3, javascript, React, web development bootcamp., Udemy E-learning

OCTOBER 2022 - MARCH 2024

front end developer Path... scrimba E-Learning bootcamp

JANUARY 2023 - APRIL 2023

working status

NOTE, Poland

I have a work permit in Poland and I am ready to relocate.